







Self-motivated individual with over 6 years of experience in customer service - predominantly in the financial sector. Strong oral and written communication skills with an excellent ability to assist a diverse customer base while rendering sound business decision. Strong leadership, analytical, and problem-solving skills with exceptional attention to detail and an innate ability to learn new skills and processes quickly and proficiently.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Personal Banker **Customer Service and Sales Representative** Wells Fargo Bank - Miami, FL

Dec. 2015 - Present Mar. 2015 - Dec. 2015

- Processing financial applications accurately while adhering to established company policies and procedures
- Establishing, retaining, and deepening relationships with banking center customers
- Collecting and analyzing customer documentation to ensure accurate validation of individuals while securing personal information
- Navigating multiple computer systems and applications to prepare documents and complete customer accounts
- Prioritizing information to ensure proper handling of time-sensitive applications

Computer/TV Product Specialist

May 2013 - Jun. 2014

Brandsmart USA - Miami, FL

- Provided professional customer service
- Provided detailed, informative product knowledge to guests
- Cross-sell products, accessories, and credit cards
- Maintained inventory of all products

Social Media Intern

Jan. 2013 - Apr. 2013

Marketeg Media and Design - Miami, FL

- Content marketing
- Blogged posts on relevant social media issues
- Reached out to social network community
- Updated social media sites with relevant, timely industry news, blogs, articles, fun facts, quotes, videos and pictures

EDUCATION

SKILLS

INTERESTS

B.A. Communication Arts/Advertising; **Minor in Marketing Applications** *University of West Florida* – Pensacola, FL

Dec. 2012

Bilingual; English/Spanish Windows/macOS **Microsoft Office** HTML/CSS GitHub

Computer Programming Photography Sports Reading **Skill Aquisition**